doostang.com 2015-06-08

# Find top finance and consulting jobs on Doostang

## Doostang Privacy Policy

This privacy policy was last modified on October 4, 2013.

We built Talent Inc., d/b/a Doostang ("Doostang") because we wanted to share jobs among friends. Your comfort and security are our top priority. As such, we are committed to offering a complete set of security options that we hope will make your experience the best possible. We want to provide you with the privacy tools necessary to control how and with whom you share your information.

This Privacy Policy is only in effect for any web pages, e-mail lists, collective non user-specific information and collective personal information collected on or through Doostang's website, located at www.doostang.com, as well as any online features, services, applications and/or programs offered by Doostang (collectively, the "Site"). If you have questions or ideas, please send them to [privacy@doostang.com](mailto:privacy@doostang.com)

## Contents

  * Personal Information.
  * Use of Personal Information.
  * Links to other websites.
  * Security Measures.
  * User Agreement.

## Personal Information.

  * Creating a profile on Doostang 
    * When you register, Doostang asks for your e-mail address, a user selected user name, and other information. Once you are a registered user you can update your profile and may provide additional preferential information (e.g. professional and academic background information, contact information etc).
    * As a registered user you can change your personal information, including your contact email address, at any time.
    * You can choose to hide your information under the Privacy Preferences in Account Settings. The options include changing the settings for if you want to be seen in searches, if you want your profile to be seen and if you want your friends list to be seen.
  * Posting a Job 
    * In posting a job opening, Doostang asks for a description of the firm, description of the position, a contact email, and other information. Once you have posted the opening, you may update it at any time through the "My Posted Jobs" section of the website. You may post openings directly from your firm, or share openings from elsewhere.

## Use of Personal Information.

  * Information that we collect is used for four main purposes. First, we collect information to improve the Site by determining which of our features, services, applications and/or programs are most popular. Second, we collect information to personalize the experience of the users of the Site. For example, users of some of the features of the Site are required to create an Account, UserID and password in order to access those features. Third, we collect information to enable our users to participate in features, services, applications, programs and/or other activities from time to time. Finally, we collect information (such as credit card information) to enable our users to purchase our products directly through the Site. 
  * Technical Information 
    * Every computer connected to the internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer's "internet Protocol", or IP, address. When a user requests a web page from the Site, our web servers automatically recognize that user's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about the user other than the IP address from which the user has accessed the Site. We may collect IP address for diagnostics, and we may collect aggregated demographic/geographic statistics, but your personal IP information will never be shared with third parties (except as part of the sale or acquisition of Doostang). 
    * From time to time, we and/or our affiliates or advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your internet browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie, by itself, cannot read data from your hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites. A cookie, by itself, does not damage your system. We may use cookies to identify and keep track of those areas of the Site that you have visited in the past in order to enhance your next visit to the Site, to streamline site usage, and for some statistical purposes. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times that you have seen an advertisement. We and our advertisers may use this information to better personalize the content, banners and promotions that you see on the Site. You can choose whether or not to accept cookies by changing the settings of your internet browser. If you choose not to accept cookies, your experience on the Site may be diminished and some features may not be available or may not work as intended. 
    * In addition to the other times or occasions on which we might disclose information about users of the Site, we might also disclose information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a legal process; (b) enforce this Privacy Policy; (c) respond to claims that any materials, documents, images, graphics, logos, designs, audio, video and any other information provided from or on the Site violates the rights of third parties; and/or (d) protect the rights, property or personal safety of Doostang, its partners or users or the public. 
  * Uploading your contacts to Doostang 
    * You may upload your contacts from Gmail, Yahoo, Hotmail, AOL, Outlook, LinkedIn, and Mac accounts by logging in through Doostang. We will never store or keep your login information. We will never sell, rent, or give access to your contact lists. We will only access your contact lists with your explicit consent.
  * Collecting and Sharing Job Information 
    * We may use demographic information about a job posting, including location, hiring firm, and other information, for statistical and development purposes.
    * In order to provide you with a better job search experience, we may provide information about you to pre-approved third party websites. You can opt-out of third party services by emailing us at [contact@doostang.com](mailto:contact@doostang.com) or directly with the third-party. 
    * In order to provide users of the Site with many of the added values and special offers of reputable organizations and retailers, we may provide some or all of your personal information to reputable third-party companies. You may also receive mailings, telephone calls and/or facsimiles from other reputable, third-party companies. Users have the option of not participating in these value added benefits by following the procedure for withholding your personal information that is set forth at the end of this Privacy Policy. 
    * After registration, Doostang may contact you via email with periodic notifications about network updates, messages, and new features and services.
    * We may transfer personal information of our users to a third party as part of the acquisition of Doostang or its assets. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy.
    * We use reasonable precautions to keep the information that is disclosed to us secure. But we cannot and will not be responsible for any breach of security by any third parties or for any actions of any third parties that receive any of the information that is disclosed to us. The Site may link to a variety of other websites and the Site may contain advertisements of third parties. We are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy policies of those websites of third parties or how they treat information about their users. 
  * Credit Card Information.
    * The Site is designed to protect the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail and any other information you provide us. Doostang is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our site. We offer the industry standard security measures available by utilizing a Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") connection. It is our practice to contact customers if a problem should arise with your purchase or if we need to send you a normal business communication regarding your purchase. 

## Links to other websites.

  * Doostang may contain links to other websites, including links to various third party service providers. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Other than under agreements with certain reputable organizations and companies, and except for third party service providers whose services you voluntarily elect to utilize, we do not share any of the personal information that you provide to us with any of the websites to which the Site links, although we may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable data with those other websites. We may also link to websites that feature Doostang trademarks and names along with trademarks and names of other companies. You should review the privacy policy on those websites, as those websites may not be under Doostang's control.

## Security Measures.

  * Doostang has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. These measures include a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to our systems and maintenance of registration information in a secure database.
  * We do our best to provide secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.
  * For certain features available through the Site, we may require the use of encryption technologies provided for your protection and/or your use of a UserID and password after setting up an Account. We use reasonable precautions to protect the privacy of your UserID, password, Account information and credit card information by utilizing an SSL connection. [CONFIRM.] Accordingly, your UserID, password, Account information and credit card information are encrypted using an SSL connection and are not expected to be read in an intelligible form as they travel to the Site. You, however, are ultimately responsible for protecting your UserID, password, Account information and credit card information from disclosure to third parties, and you are not permitted to circumvent the use of required encryption technologies. You agree to: (a) immediately notify Doostang of any unauthorized use of your UserID, password and/or Account, and/or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit from your Account at the end of each session. While we may provide certain encryption technologies and use other reasonable precautions to protect your confidential information and provide suitable security, we do not and cannot guarantee or warrant that information transmitted through the internet is secure, or that such transmissions are free from delay, interruption, interception or error.

## Information From Children. 

  * The Site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of thirteen (13). We do not collect personally identifiable data from any person that we know to be under the age of thirteen (13). If we learn that a user under the age of thirteen (13) is publicly posting or sharing personally identifiable information on or through the Site, then we will use reasonable measures to block that user from accessing these areas of the Site. 
  * Parents should be aware that Doostang's Privacy Policy will govern our use of personal data, but also that information that is voluntarily given by children – or others – in chat sessions, e-mail exchanges, bulletin boards or the like may be used by other parties to generate unsolicited communications. Doostang encourages all parents to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their personal data while using the internet.

## European Union Users.

  * Because Doostang's Site is accessible globally, the information that we collect may be made available to our affiliates, partners and subsidiaries worldwide. For those users visiting us from the European Union, please note that Doostang may transfer your personally identifiable data outside the European Union for use for any of the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. By using the Site and providing Doostang with your personal data, you consent to such transfer of your personal data. 

## User Agreement.

  * As a user of Doostang you will have access to other users' personal information. You agree to use this information solely for recruiting purposes. Doostang and its users shall not tolerate spam of any kind. Accounts suspected of causing spam will be deactivated immediately. Please feel free to report any misuse of Doostang by contacting us at [contact@doostang.com](mailto:contact@doostang.com). 
  * Your use of the Doostang website, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and Doostang's Terms and Conditions. . We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the top of this page to determine if the Policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of the Doostang website following the posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes. 

## Governing Law; Exclusive Jurisdiction

  * This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the State of California without regard to its conflict of law provisions. Any disputes arising under or related in any way to this Privacy Policy, the Site, any Application or any Services shall be resolved solely through binding arbitration in Santa Clara County, California, in accordance with the JAMS rules then in effect, and judgment upon any award rendered in such arbitration will be binding and conclusive on the parties hereto and may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof. 

## Your Consent To This Privacy Policy

  * By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as specified above or as we otherwise see fit unless you inform us otherwise by means of the procedure identified below. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will make an effort to post those changes on this web page so that you will always be able to understand what information we collect, how we use that information and under what circumstances we may disclose that information to others. We may use comments, information or feedback that you may submit in any manner that we may choose without notice or compensation to you. 
  * If you have additional questions or comments of any kind, if you see anything on the Site that you think is inappropriate or if you would like to have any or all of your personal information withheld from third party organizations and companies and/or from third party service providers, please let us know by e-mail contact@doostang.com or by sending your comments or requests to: 
  * Talent Inc., d/b/a Doostang   
254 W 31st Street   
12th Floor   
New York, NY 10014 

Attn: Customer Care – Website Issues
